The Honeymoon is a comedy film directed by Dean Craig.
Englishman Adam and his American bride Sarah are about to embark on
the romantic honeymoon of a lifetime in Venice, Italy.
But when the newlyweds’ trip is gatecrashed by Adam’s excessively needy best friend, Ed, it
inadvertently turns their perfect lovers’ holiday into a complete disaster.
Adam, played by Pico Alexander.
Sarah, played by Maria Bakalova.
Bav, played by Asim Chaudhry.
Giorgio, played by Lucas Bravo.
Adam 18 y.o., played by Flynn Allen.
Lucas, played by Kai Portman.
The Honeymoon is a 2022 romantic comedy film written and directed by Dean Craig.
It stars Maria Bakalova and Pico Alexander as a newly married couple whose honeymoon in
Venice is derailed by the groom's needy best friend Bav (Asim Chaudhry).
Lucas Bravo stars as an Italian gangster.
The Honeymoon received a limited release in the United States on 16 December
2022, and was simultaneously available digitally and on-demand.
In the United Kingdom and other European countries, it
was released on Amazon Prime Video.
The tone is lighthearted.